那没有常性的月亮，
"Oh swear not by by the moon,
三十天里它竟会
the inconstant moon,
变上几回圆缺。
that monthly changes in her circled orb,
免得你的爱就象月亮一样变化无常。
lest that thy love prove likewise,variable."
那该拿什么起誓呢？
"What shall I swear by?"
Hey!
现在是在朗读罗密欧与朱莉叶懂吗？
We're trying to do a little "Romeo and Juliet" here!
不需要感觉迟钝的蠢货来煞风景！
We don't need no insensitive jerk,messing it up.
对不起教练。
I'm sorry Coach.
算了。你继续念罗密欧发誓的那一段。
Alright...err...go back to the part where Romeo was thwearing.
好了，同学们，
Ok,people.
记得下星期要考
Remember next week we have a major exam
莎士比亚的十四行诗，
on all the Shakespeare Sonnets.
一定要把节奏和韵律念出来。
So you better know your assonants from your elbows.
走吧，Carol，你怎么了？
Are you coming Carol,or what?
如今哪有像罗密欧这么重感情的人？
Where are sensitive men,like Romeo,nowadays?
那么能哭敢哭的男人。
Men,who aren't afraid to cry.
可现在有些男人听莎士比亚就会睡觉。
I mean,all we have are insensitive jocks.
你认为汤姆克鲁斯会哭吗？
Do you think Tom Cruise Cries?
他想干什么都能行。
Tom Cruise can do anything he wants.
Seaver!
什么事，罗布克先生？
Yes,Mr. Lovett.
对你说一句让你震惊的话，
I'm gonna say something to you that might shock you.
这个班只有你，能和我媲美。
But in this class,I consider you my equal.
我是说
Well,what I mean is,
如果我有个关于莎士比亚的问题，
if I had a question about Shakespeare,
并且能问他也能问你，
and I had a choice of either asking him or you;
我会问你。
I'd ask you.
噢，谢谢。
Well thank you.
这和他总是穿着紧身服跑来跑去
And it has nothing to do with the fact that
并无关系。
they ran around in tights all the time.
我是说想让你帮帮我，
And the point is,is that I need your help.
说真的，
It's no big secret that
要不是奥布太太生病的话，
I wouldn't even be teaching this class,
我是根本不会来教这门课的。懂我的意思吗？
if Mrs. Orbeaux hadn't gone a little bit flaky,if you know what I mean?
是这样的，班上有位同学他要不及格了，
But there's a kid who's flunking the class,
我感到我有责任。
who shouldn't be and I kind o' blame myself.
所以我在想，也许你能辅导他。
So,I was wondering if,maybe you could tutor him.
我觉得我这个人当不了辅导……
Well,I've never really thought of myself as a ...
老师。
teacher.
谁说的？你同意吗？
Hey,who has? So what do you say?
好吧，让我试一试。
Ok,I'll give it a shot.
好，对！波比。
Ah,yeah. Hey,Bobby!
这个运动员？
The jock?
来了教练。
Yo,Coach!!
听着波比，
Now,Bobby.
Seaver她想要帮你通过莎士比亚考试。
Seaver here's gonna help you through all that Shakespeare stuff...
好极了。
Alright.
现在你完全得听她的，
Now,look! You do everything she says,
你不通过考试就不准踢球，
because,if you don't pass,you don't play.
把眼睛哭红了也没有用
And it aint gonna do you no good comin' crying your eyes out to me;
就像你去年出现过的那样
like you did last year.
还没正式介绍过呢。我是波比·温尼特。
I don't thing we ever really met. I'm Bobby Winette.
我知道。
I know.
你是才女Carol。
And you're Carol,"The Brain".
我知道。
I know.
你去年真的把眼哭红了。
You actually cried last year?
是的。
Yeah.
我尿急了。
Groin pull.
-= Subripped by Susie Shi =-       2007.07.29
谁啊？
Hello.
我可不是你的病人，爸爸，
It's not one of your mental patients,Dad,
是我。
it's just me.
回来得早啊，Ben。
Hey,you're home early,Ben.
是的，我们老师食物中毒了
Yeah,my teacher got food poisoning
吃了食堂里的鱼
from the "Tuna Surprise" in the cafeteria.
她说真是没想到。
She was surprised alright.
她没事吧？
Is she OK?
可能的，
I guess.
刚上课凯特老师还在给我们
Alls I know is that one minute Miss Cutter was reading off
念小鱼本事大，可一下
"The Little Fish That Could",and the next minute,
她就倒在窗台上了。
she was rowfing out the window.
HI，爸爸，知道我们学校怎么样？
Hey,Dad! Ask me how school went today!
准没好事。
I'm afraid to...
是好事爸爸，健康课来了个小测验，
It went great Dad we had this pop quiz in health class
我得了个，一个优！
and got ... Are you ready for this?... an A!!!
是优？
An A?
对！
Yeah!
祝贺你啊。
Great news son.
瞧
Yeah,Yeah. See,
要我们列举食物的四个类别
we had to list the four basic food groups,
我每一个都写对了。
and I got every single one of 'em right.
哗！
Wow!
温习两小时真是没白费。
Those two hours of studying really paid off.
HI,爸爸。
Hi Dad.
Hi.
Mike你回来了？
Mike,you're home!!
Ben？你也回来了？
Ben,you're home too!!
爸爸，你让Mike把Ben带走好吗？
Dad,would you make Mike take Ben some place.
你建议带哪去？
Any place in particular?
最好是去北京。
Beijing would be good.
你为什么突然要
Look! How come all of a sudden,
撵我们走？
you don't want us around?
不是突然。
It's not sudden.
Carol!
Carol？
我明白了爸爸，
Oh,no,no,no,I get it Dad.
她一定是想带回个什么有头脑的朋友，
She's probably got one of her "oh so brainy friends" coming over
怕我们会使她难堪，
and she's afraid that we'll embarrass her.
当然了，我们会那样的。
Which of course we will.
我带谁回来当你没有任何关系。
It's none of your business,who I've got coming over.
Carol，以你的兄弟为羞耻可不好。
Look,Carol,being ashamed of your brothers,is not nice.
对！
Yeah.
有时会更糟。
Could've been worse.
好了，谁愿意和我一块去接你们的母亲？--
Which one of you guys wants to come with me to pick up your Mom?
请吃冰淇淋。
Free ice-cream.
快走！
Let's roll.
我可不希望你去打扰他们
And I don't want you to be bothering your sister
当你妹妹的小朋友来，
when her little friend is here.
我不会的爸爸。
Hey,no sweat Dad.
Mike，你干嘛不找个地方去数数你的脑细胞？！
Mike,why don't you go some place and count your brain cell?
你怎么了？
What is it with you?
究竟是谁要来？
Who's coming over?
至高无上的小丑皇后！
The...the geek queen of Dewey High?
你管得也太宽了！
It's none of your business.
哦，明白了，
Oh. I get it.
不是什么小丑皇后，
This isn't just like a she-geek,
是小丑国王。是吗？
this is a he-geek,isn't it?
你这个无赖！
You're scum.
说吧，是谁？象棋俱乐部的肌肉男？
So,who is it? Like a hunk from the chess club?
还是荣誉协会的书呆子？
A total babe from the honors society?
你就别费劲了，
For your information,
我告诉你吧，他是大学足球队的队长。
it happens to be the Captain of the varsity football team.
波比·温尼特？
Bobby Winette?
对！
Yeah.
哦，等一下。
Wow...wai...wait a minute.
波比到咱们家来，来看你？！
Bobby Winette is coming over here to see you?
是的！
Yeah.
干嘛？
Why?
来了，请看！
There. See?
你好。
Err...hello.
哟，波比！是你啊！
Yo! Bobby! My man!
你好吗老兄？
How in the heck are you doing bro?
很好！Mark？对吗？
Fine. Mark,right?
哦……对，最好的朋友是这样叫的！
Yeah,yeah,that's what my close friends call me.
好，Carol，去哪温课？
So,Carol,where do you wanna study?
哈哈，你找他原来是为了去温课！
Aha. That explains why you'd be over here seeing her.
去我的房间，
Well,how about my room?
这样就可以少一些愚蠢的干扰！
There'll be fewer stupid interruptions.
你父母不介意？
Your parents won't mind?
这就是咱们俩，
Well,we're the only ones here.
当然还有那个Mark！
Except for Mark,of course.
波比我真搞不懂，罗密欧自杀前干嘛不对茱莉叶
Bobby,I don't know why Romeo didn't try CPR
好好检查一下。
on Juliet before he killed himself.
他连脉搏也不搭一下
I mean,the guy doesn't even check the pulse,
就把命赔上了！
before he does himself in.
波比，要知道这是一出四百年前写的戏，
Bobby,the play is over four hundred years old.
是古典作品。
It's a Classic.
听着，对你们天才来说，
Look! To you geniuses,
茱莉叶吃了从牧师那弄的药装死
it may make sense that Juliet gets some drug from a priest,
也是有道理的。
and pretends like she's dead,
以至于她可以和那个傻小子私奔，他连打电话
so that she can run off with a guy who's too stupid to pick up the phone
叫医生都不会
and call a doctor.
可对我这号人，是种破玩意。
Well,to a guy like me,it's sheep dip!!
你把莎士比亚的戏叫破玩意？
You're calling Shakespeare,"sheep dip"?
如果我是罗密欧，你是茱莉叶,
If I was Romeo,and you were Juliet
如果我这么爱你的话，
and I really had it bad for you,
不管是什么，也阻挡不了。
there's nothing nobody could say that would get in the way...
不管你的家庭，我的家庭，不管什么，
not my family,not your family,not nobody.
等大家明白过来你们早就开到
By the time those people turned around to look for you and me,
快到新泽西州了！
we'd be in my pick-up,half way to Jersey!!
很抱歉我太冲动了。
I'm sorry I lost my temper.
有时我会被感情所左右，
Sometimes my emotions get the best of me.
甚至控制不了。
I guess I'm too sensitive.
这没关系。这东西我也不想要了。
It's OK. I really didn't want it anymore,anyway.
看来辅导也不能解决问题。
This tutoring stuff's a bad idea.
是我太笨了。
My head's too thick.
不不不不，
No,no,no,no,no.
要知道理解莎士比亚是一件很难的事情。
Understanding Shakespeare is a very difficult thing to do.
我刚开始读的时候几个月也领悟不了，
You know,when I first read his plays I was lost for months;
六年级一年我全耗上了。
it ruined my entire sixth grade year.
你六年级就念这玩意了？
You read this stuff in the sixth grade?
是怪人，对吗？
I'm weird,OK?
不不不不，你很聪明。
No,no,no!! You're smart.
天哪，为我浪费那么多时间你一定很没劲，对吗？
Boy,spending this much time with me must really be boring for you?
那倒不是的。
Not really.
呃，读到哪了？
So where were we?
每个人都死了。
Everybody was dead.
晚饭有鱼吃，Ben，过半小时回来。
Dinner in half an hour Ben! Tuna Surpri
啊！
Aargghh!!
孩子们！
Hey guys!
HI，Mike，爸爸说你健康课得了个优？
Hey Mike. Dad told me about your A in health.
对。呵呵。你说说食物基本类别有哪四种？
Yeah. Come on Mike,let's hear those four basic food groups!
呆会再谈好吗？我现在要去打会儿球
Yeah,maybe later Dad. I'm gonna shoot a few,OK?
呵呵。Carol在哪？
Where's Carol?
和一个足球运动员在她的卧室里。
Upstairs in her bedroom with a football player.
足球运动员？
Football player?
咱们这个儿子有很强的幽默感。
Our son has a very weird sense of humour.
呵，对，就爱逗Carol。
Yeah,little kill.
HI，爸爸妈妈，这是波比。
Hi Mom,Dad,this is Bobby.
你们好。
Please to meet you.
是足球运动员？
The football player?
你知道我？
Yeah,you heard of me?
对，可我不相信。
Yeah,I just didn't believe it.
Carol，怎么回事？
Carol,what's going on here?
我在辅导波比。
I'm tutoring Bobby.
噢，原来是这么一回事。
Oh,well that makes sense.
对，她在把莎士比亚译成英语。
Yeah. Carol's translating this Shakespeare guy into English.
很高兴看到你波比。
Well,nice to meet you Bobby.
这荣誉是我的，Seaver夫人。Seaver先生。
The pleasure was distinctly mine Mrs. Seaver. Mr. Seaver.
噢，足球。
Yo. Football.
噢，对了Carol，明天见。
Oh,Carol,I'll see you tomorrow.
再次谢谢你。
Thanks again.
这孩子不错。
Nice boy.
对。
Yeah.
非常有礼貌。
Certainly was polite.
对。
Yeah.
而且很帅。
And cute.
对。
Yeah.
你眼力不错，Maggie。
You're doing great Maggie.
你说说，觉得他怎么样？
So,what do you think of him?
妈妈，我只是辅导，
Oh,Mom. I'm just tutoring him.
他不是我要的类型。
He's not my type,OK?
我搞不懂你为什么会以为
I swear,I don't know where you'd ever get the idea
吸引我的是身体…..波比。
I'd be attracted to body...Bobby.
你没必要这么激动，宝贝。
No reason to get excited,honey.
于是，你就和他单独地呆在房间里了？
So,you were alone in your bedroom with a boy; so what?
在这种情况下要问我相信谁那就你。
If there's anybody we could trust in a situation like that,it's you.
是这样的，宝贝。
That's right,honey.
你们信任我？
You trust me?
那当然。
You bet.
这话说得也太糟糕了！
What a rotten thing for you to say.
我是说我们对你放心。
I mean we have faith in you.
为什么你们都以为我要干的事总是对的？
Why does everybody always think,I'm gonna do the right thing.
这就是说你对波比感兴趣啰？
So,you're saying that you're interested in Bobby?
妈妈，我的话难道你没听进去？
Mom. Haven't you heard a word I've said?
我认为他没有男子汉的品质！
He has none of the qualities I would look for in a boy.
是哪些品质？
Well,what are those qualities?
他的智力必须发达，
He'd have to be an intellectual;
至少和我差不多，最好胜我一筹
at least as smart as I am,if not smarter.
他应当重感情而且很敏感，
He'd have to sensitive and vulnerable too,
对宇宙和人类的地位
with a full understanding of the universe,
有充分的了解。
and our place in it.
这下放心了，
Well,we're safe.
他排除了所有的人，除了卡尔·赛特。
She's eliminated everybody but Karl Sagin.
请等一下，是什么光从那窗户里透出？
"What soft white light,through yonder window breaks?
那是…..
It is the..."
有什么问题？
What do you want?
请你解释一下。
Can you explain what that means?
这是一个比喻，
Well,it's an analogy,
莎士比亚借用罗密欧的口
wherein Shakespeare likens the presence
把茱莉叶比作刚升起的太阳，
of Juliet to that of the rising sun.
你这个傻瓜！
You chuckle head!
好吧，晚上请你们回去预习一下无事生非，
OK,I want you to read the first act of "Much Ado About Nothing",
准备讲讲无事生非都是生些什么非。
and be prepared to talk about what all the...err..."do" is about.
很好，又布置作业了。
Oh great,more homework.
今天才星期二我快要落下来了。
It's only Tuesday and I'm already getting behind.
说到落下来，
Speaking of getting behind,
我想放学以后谁愿意去看男生的游泳训练？
does anyone wanna go watch the boys' swim team practise after school?
我看这太没意思了。
That is so dumb.
Carol，你怎么从来不娱乐？
Carol,don't you ever have any fun?
Carol，呆会到你家碰头。
Carol,I'll see you after school at your place.
好的。
OK.
她真行！
She does!
请问你现在和波比到了什么程度了？
So,like what is this Bobby Winette situation?
没什么程度，我只是帮他辅导。
There's no situation,I'm just tutoring him.
呵，怪不得呢。
Oh,well what figures.
你说这话是什么意思？
And what is that supposed to mean?
我也不知道。
Well,I don't know.
Carol，你别见怪，
Oh,come on Carol,don't have a cow!
每个人都知道你……你很清白。
Everybody knows,you're immaculate.
我，我很清白？
Immaculate?
就是正经，
You know,wholesome.
还有更糟的，比如说，嗯，发胖！
Well,there are worse things to be...errm...like fat.
那我，就对你们说了吧，
Well,for your information,
波比和我一起温课，每天都在我的卧室里，
Bobby and I did our studying all evening in my bedroom.
温习的功课是罗密欧与茱莉叶。
And the subject was "Romeo and Juliet",
这下你们懂了？
if you get my meaning.
既然我已经能够像一个成熟的女人，
You know,maybe I don't have to ogle the boys' swim team
干嘛我还要去死盯着男生们游泳呢？！
and act like a little girl,when I can be a woman,at home.
猜猜怎么了！
Guess what?
Carol Seaver和波比，在一起过夜了！
Carol Seaver spent the night with Bobby the Boy.
谁啊？
Hello
是我，爸爸。你最喜欢的小孩。
It's me Dad,your favourite kid.
哦，进来吧，Carol。
Oh,well come on in Carol.
是我，是我，是我，爸爸。
Oh,hardy ha ha ha.
学校怎么样？
So,how was school today?
很好。
OK.
爸爸，大事不好了。
Dad,we got big trouble!
Mike，到底怎么了？
Mike! What happened to you?
你必须走开，
Ben,look,you're gonna have to leave;
我和爸爸现在是男人间的谈话。
me and Dad have got some man talk alright!
我干嘛不能听？！
What am I? A Muppet?
Mike，你是不是又打架了？
Mike,you look like you've been in a fight!
是的。
Oh yeah!
你跟谁打了？
Well,who with?
是跟我们那个演讲班。
My sixth period speech class.
你跟全班打了？
What,you fought the whole class?
我说不准。
Look,I don't know Dad,
我被压在最底下，
I was at the bottom of the pile. Look,
打架问题现在并不重要，
my fight is not important right now,
罚我停课也一样。
neither is my suspension.
罚你停课了？！
You were suspended?
是的。听着，
Yeah. Look,alright.
上课刚开始。艾迪过来问我
At the start of the class,everybody comes up to me
有没有听说新闻，
and asks if I've heard the news.
我说，什么新闻。他说是Carol的，
I say,"what news?","about Carol".
我一向认为Carol最多不过有些书呆子趣闻。
Well,you know me,I'm always ready for a good Carol nerd story.
可接下去，他讲了Carol很多难听的话，
Yeah,and then he starts saying this disgusting stuff about Carol.
我笑着还以为他逗我玩呢。
So,I keep smiling,you see,and waiting for the punch line;
可他是真的，
only he's not kidding.
我也不知道怎么了
And I don't know what happened but the next thing I know,
就一拳头把他给打倒了。
I was in there punching Eddie out.
我又是踢又是打的，
And then I was in there swinging and kicking,
我不知道干嘛要那样生气。
and I couldn't even figure out why I was so angry.
我当时真是豁出命去保护Carol，
I'm here I was,getting all busted up,protecting Carol!!
难道我脑袋发晕？
I must have been delirious.
慢着，他们是怎么说Carol的？
Wait a minute. But,well,what were they saying about Carol?
他们是这么说的，说她和波比
Well,that she's been...sleeping with Bobby Winette,
在她房间里睡觉。
right up in her own room!
哦，这话可是没有根据。
Oh. That doesn't even make any sense.
我也是这么说的，
Yeah,tell me about it!
波比要是想造点谣言，
I mean if Bobby wants to start a rumour,
他就该挑像吉娜·勃壳维茨那样的人。
why didn't he just pick someone like Sheena Birkov?
怎么会是她…
Now with her...
肯定是波比说的？
Hey,Mike! Are you sure Bobby said this?
肯定，爸爸。
Yes Dad!
我认为你不该让他再来咱们家。
Look,I don't think you should let Bobby come over here anymore.
这会他和Carol在楼上。
Well,he's upstairs with Carol,right now.
我去把他揪下来。
You hold him,I'll knock him over.
Mike，我来和他谈好吗？
Mike,I'll talk to him,alright?
我错过了"男人间的谈话"吗？
Hi,am I too late for the man talk?
你又打架了？！
Were you in a fight?
哪只打架，都闹翻天了。
Not just a fight; a brawl.
对，是为了保护他妹妹的好名声。
Yeah. Protecting his sister's good name.
对。有我在，谁也别想中伤那丫头！
Yeah. Nobody bad-mouths that geek,when I'm around!
从我的嘴唇上
"Then have my lips,
洗净那个罪过
the sin that they have took."
好了，茱莉叶说罗密欧的吻就是罪过，
Now,Juliet means that Romeo's first kiss,the sin,
洗涮的人就是罗密欧。
should be taken back by Romeo.
好像是暗示罗密欧再吻一次？
Sounds like she's scamming him for another kiss?
是这样！
Exactly!
好极了！
Alright!
好，这里
OK. Here.
沾上我的罪过，oh,侵。。。
"Sin from my lips,oh tre...tre...tre..."
侵犯
Trespass.
多么甜蜜
"...Trespass sweetly urged.
把我的罪过还我吧。
Give me my sin again."
男的已经了解他的用意了。
So,he gets the message,right?
很对，
Right!
他们俩就亲了，
And then they kiss,
再一次表示了爱情。
restating their love,
虽然他俩来自不同的世界。
even though they are from two different worlds.
Carol.
Carol？
什么？
Yes.
你非常聪明！
You're really...smart.
真走运。
Lucky me.
我是说非常美好。
Oh,no,I mean it's nice!
我从来没有和聪明姑娘打过交道。
I...I...I never hung out with a smart girl before;
真是太有意思了。
it's interesting.
股票市场才有意思呢。
The stock market is interesting.
我是说非常美好。
I mean,it's kind o' nice.
你是说美好？
Nice,is nice.
有一家剧院正在上演罗密欧和茱莉叶，
There's this theatre that's showing "Romeo and Juliet",
我想如果你有空，
and I was wondering if you had nothing to do,
咱们就可以……
you and I could...
爸爸妈妈？
Mom! Dad!
我诚恳地希望没有打扰你们什么。
I sincerely hope we aren't interrupting anything.
呃，下午好。Seaver先生，夫人。
A...a...afternoon Mr. and Mrs. Seaver.
波比，我想和你说一句。
Bobby,I wanna have a word with you.
爸爸你干嘛？
Dad,what are you doing?
我想和跟说一句，Carol。
And I'd like a word with you,Carol.
太让我难堪啦。
This is so embarrassing.
波比，到办公室，
Bobby,my office.
把你的书带上。
You can take your books.
妈妈，你有都没有想过你都干了些什么？
Mother,do you have any idea what you have just done?
我当然想过……
I certainly do.
你把我的一生全都毁了！
You have ruined my entire life.
Carol，发生什么事，我看你并不了解。
Carol,I don't think you understand what is going on.
我来告诉你发生了什么吧！
I'll tell you what's going on.
有一位足球队的队长。
The captain of the football team,
他是杜维中学的骄傲，
the pride of the Dewey Hooters
他刚想邀请我一起出去，
was in the middle of asking me out.
我，才女Carol Seaver！
Me! Carol "The Brain" Seaver!
哦，宝贝，这话真不该由我来说，
Oh,honey,I hate to be the one to tell you this
可波比并不像我们看上去那样好。
but Bobby isn't as nice as he might seem.
你怎么知道的？
How would you know?
因为他在外面大造你的谣言!
Because,he's saying terrible things about you.
你在说些什么呀!
What are you talking about?
他对每个人都说了，
He's been telling people,
包括全学校，
all over school,
你和他单独在一起亲热。
that while you two were supposed to be studying,
就在睡你这。
you slept together.
他讲的？
He's telling?
可是我不希望你把这个任意诽谤我女儿的人
And I don't want someone who would spread those kinds of rumours
带到我们的家里来。
about my daughter,in this house.
听我说妈妈，恐怕这里面有误会。
Well,Mom...erm... I think we have a problem then.
说吧。
Well?
说什么？
Well,what?
当然是说你自己。
Explain yourself!
哦，是说我在哪出生，说我踢球的位置？
Oh,you mean,like where I was born,what position I play!
不，说说你昨天在学校里说了些什么话？
No. I'm talking about what you said at school yesterday.
什么话？
What do you mean?
你说过的谎话？
The lie you told.
哦，你怎么知道的？
Oh. How did you know?
每个人都知道！
Everyone knows.
好吧，我并没有真的读过《白鲸》。
OK. I didn't really read Moby Dick.
我知道图书馆有一套
The library has these old kind o' books,
著名的连环画，我也只不过是……
called Classic Illustrated and all I did was...
可我指的是Carol！
I'm talking about Carol!
哦，她肯定读过原著，她什么都读过。
Oh,I bet she read it. She's read everything.
这话我就对戴碧和雪丽说过！
I just read it to Debby and Shelly.
我真没想到她们会传遍整个学校！
I mean I never thought they'd go blab it all over the whole school with it!!
你就别提戴碧和雪丽了！
Oh,forget about Debby and Shelly.
我干嘛不提？
I'd like to.
她们怎么可以这样！
I mean,how could they do that?
她们怎么可以相信这号事呢？！
How could they believe something like that?
是你自己对她们说的。
Because they heard it from you!
妈妈，别为她们辩护。
Mom,don't defend them.
Carol，你干嘛要凭空造出这样的流言。
Carol,how could you start a rumour like that about...
确实是谣言？
It is a rumour,isn't it?
你应该知道，妈妈。
Of course it is Mom. I mean,
我看人人都知道，一个正派，清白慎重的Carol是
everybody knows that,decent,responsible,immaculate Carol
绝不敢做那种事的。
wouldn't dare do a thing like that.
那为什么？
Then,why?
我也不知道。
I don't know.
这是个Mike式的回答，
Carol,that's a Mike answer.
希望你能多说几句。
I expect a little more from you.
我是圣徒吗？
What am I,a saint?
那你为什么老说，
Why do you always have to say,
Mike，你干嘛不象你妹妹那样？
"Mike,why can't you be more like your sister?"
为什么每位老师都要叫我来代管整个班级
Why does every teacher I've ever had put me in charge,
当他们离开教室的时候
when they leave the class room?
为什么学校开任何会议每次都把我叫去当记录员呢？
Why is it that I'm the one,always to be elected a recording secretary?
噢，宝贝，这些全都是好事。
Oh,honey,those are all good things.
可有的时候，
I just wish,that every once in a while,
我也很想去偶尔当一回
it would be nice to thought of as...
危险分子
dangerous.
寻找刺激？
Provocative?
是的。
Yes.
性感？
Sexy?
对。
Yes.
你想当那种不该跟动员员
The kind o' girl that should never be allowed
关在同一屋里的女孩子？
to study in her bedroom with a hunk?
对。
Yes.
你有没有注意到。。。波比可爱的臀部？
Have you noticed...Bobby's cute bottom?
妈妈？
Mom?
又是我错了？
What,am I wrong?
不。
No!!!
听着宝贝，学校里的流言蜚语必须去澄清。
You know honey,you're gonna have to clear up this rumour at school.
哦，对。可是能不能够
Oh yeah. Do you think it could...erm...
过几天再说？
wait a couple of days?
我没办法了，
Bobby,you leave me no choice.
只有通知你的父母。
I'm gonna phone your parents!
为什么？
Why?
为什么？！因为你到处跟人家说
Why? Because you told anybody who would listen,
你和Carol……
that you and Carol...
在一起温课。
Studied together!!!
什么？
What?
这件事是要我保密吗？
Was I supposed to keep that a secret?
JASON，没问题了。
Jason,it's alright.
你别插嘴。
Hold on!!
你别说了。
Hold off!!
可是他--
But,he...
并没有--
Didn't...
哦
Ah!
做--
Do...
可是--
But I...
任何事情。相信我吧。
Anything. Trust me.
波比，Carol在等你听课呢。
Bobby,Carol's waiting to finish your lesson...
不过是在客厅里。
in the living room.
谢谢你没有通过我的父母。Seaver先生，
Thanks for not calling my folks Mr. Seaver.
我保证明天第一件事
I promise the first thing tomorrow,
把《白鲸》从头到尾全部读完！
I'm gonna read Moby Dick,cover to cover.
Hi.
HI，
HI，你家里的人真是有点奇怪。
Hi. You have a very strange family.
我认为他们都很正常。
Oh,they seem pretty normal to me.
好吧，讲到哪了？哦，对了，
OK,where were we? Oh yeah,
我记得你讲过罗密欧和茱莉叶的那场电影？
you were saying something about Romeo and Juliet the movie.
噢，对！你是否愿意？
I was gonna ask you,if you'd...
我很愿意。
I'd love to.
那我回家换衣服。
Right,well,I'm gonna go and get ready.
为什么？你看上去非常好--我是说--
Why? You look incredible. I mean...errm...
你打算什么时候来接我？
What time are you gonna be picking me up?
一小时后。
An hour?
很好，我也需要换换衣服。
Fine. I may change too.
Carol--你非常可爱。
Carol,I think you're real neat.
HI，不准在我妹妹背后说坏话？！
Hey! Nobody says that about my sister!!
莎士比亚？
Hmmm. Shakespeare.
麦克白？
Macbeth.
出去，讨厌的斑点！
"Out,out damn spot!"
呵，这个人有条狂狗。
Ah,so the guy had a dog.